defencetalk.com 2014-12-17

# Privacy Policy | DefenceTalk | Defense & Military News - Forums - Pictures - Weapons

[pagelist 2]DefenceTalk.com (hereafter referred to as DefenceTalk), is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors, members and all users of our internet services. The following Privacy Policy outlines how DefenceTalk treats personal information received about you when you visit our web sites.

If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices, please contact us by email at admin@defencetalk.com with the subject heading “Privacy Policy” or visit our Feedback form.

Partners of DefenceTalk and other websites you may access via DefenceTalk have different privacy policies and are not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you read the privacy statement of each such website to find out how they treat and protect your personal information.

**Collection and Use of User Details**

**Voluntary Information**

When you register, and at other times, DefenceTalk collects personally identifiable information that you provide voluntarily which includes such details as your name, address, job title and function, organization, e-mail address and other information that you may provide.

DefenceTalk.com uses personal information in the following ways: · To enable us to process, validate and verify subscriptions or any other service · To notify you of new products, promotions and services from DefenceTalk · To allow us to deliver content and advertising based on your characteristics and/or personal preferences

**Statistical Information**

DefenceTalk collects IP address and web site usage data information in aggregate form so that no individual user is identified.

DefenceTalk uses information in aggregate form in the following ways: · To enhance and develop content and services · To aid future strategic development · To plan for the maintenance and development of system software, hardware and communications technology. · To provide advertisers with data on the number of users and usage patterns

**Cookies**

1\. Session Cookie. When you log in or register on a DefenceTalk web site, DefenceTalk’s web servers send a string of text called a “cookie” to your browser, which stores it in its memory. The text identifies DefenceTalk and includes a string of numbers that represent your rights to access restricted material on DefenceTalk’s web sites. As your browser connects to DefenceTalk sites, it automatically sends the cookie information back to DefenceTalk’s servers so that your access rights can be determined very quickly. In addition to this, some of our services (Forums, Gallery, etc.) need to recall selections you have made during your session so that they display the correct information to you. In both cases, when you close your browser, this cookie information disappears. It is never written to a file on your machine.

The second area is on Police Review where we use persistent cookies to prevent the re-appearance of the poll and the main entry pages, this is done to improve the user experience. If you do not accept cookies then these will always re-appear.

Security DefenceTalk takes physical, electronic and managerial steps to maintain the security and accuracy of personally identifiable information we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. However, DefenceTalk makes no representation, warranty or guarantee that such information will remain secure and accurate at all times. In addition, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to DefenceTalk, and you do so at your own risk.

Children’s Privacy Protecting children’s privacy is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information from individuals we actually know are under 13, and no DefenceTalk web site/webpage is targeted to attract anyone under 13. We request that all visitors under 13 to a DefenceTalk webs site not disclose or provide any personally identifiable information. If we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete the child’s personally identifiable information from our records.

Legal Requirements We may provide access to your personally identifiable information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of a DefenceTalk web site, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors of a DefenceTalk web site or the public. In those instances, the information is provided only for that purpose.

In the event DefenceTalk goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

Changes to this statement Due to changes in legislation and best practice or enhancements to functionality and content on Defencetalk we may make changes to our privacy policy and will reflect those changes in this statement, so you should check here from time to time.
